Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
The Meaning Behind Sunflowers
Memories of summer...
What?! Go head-to-head?
Sounds like this only got out of hand
because of Onii-chan!
I won't deny that.
There's no way Yu can win
if he's getting judged by Kureha-san!
I'll just decline her offer,
and you can pay off my debt!
We're only in this mess because
you lied about going to Tokyo.
You're liable for this!
The Inuzuka Family won't get involved!
Come on! Have a heart!
I still can't believe she
wants Yu-kun to pay this off.
She's rotten to the core.
Next time she's home, I'll take her to Mom
if I have to drag her myself.
Kureha will resort to anything
if it means meeting her goal.
She channeled all her negative energy
into getting to the top, after all.
Negative energy?
Like when people make fun of her.
It just fuels her fire.
She's the opposite of you.
Y-Yeah.
You work hard for people who support you.
To her, you guys aren't passionate enough.
Not that there's a right or wrong.
Then what if I ran away?
Knowing Kureha, she'll stick to the rules.
But I imagine she'll at least
open her own store next to yours.
Then invest a bunch of money
to put you out of business.
That's not even funny.
Yu-kun, no need to worry.
If you lose, feel free to hand Himari over.
That way, you can open your store with me!
Thanks, I'll make sure not to lose then!
Anyways, just do your best as usual.
Remember, I'm here because I fell
for your accessories.
Y-Yeah.
Either way, I have to win
for Himari to stay.
That's right. I have no time to waste.
I've been spoiled by the people
around me for too long.
My work has to attract
people who don't know me.
Like Saku-nee-san said,
I can't stay frozen in time!
There he is. Yu!
Come on, let's go look for summer memories!
That sounded so cheesy.
Even I feel embarrassed.
Well it's summer break.
This is the cheesiest time of our lives!
Don't forget, you're
the one who's on the line here.
It's fine, I know you'll win!
And I have a backup plan just in case.
Backup plan?
I'll join their agency then quit right away!
You know, that's how you
always set people off.
Besides, that means you'd
have to drop out of school.
Like that's a problem?
You'd take care of me for life, right?
D-Don't phrase it like that!
It's misleading.
We'll be co-owners. Okay?
Phrase it like what?
Well, I mean... it sounds like...
Marriage, you know?
Huh?
When have I ever said
that I don't mean it like that?
You promised to only have eyes
for me, remember?
Himari, I promise
to win against Kureha-san—
Bwa-ha!
It's been a while since I got you!
Himari!
You've been kinda cold recently.
Make me "Bwa-ha!" some more.
What kind of a request is that?
Yu-kun, Hii-chan.
Hey, Enocchi!
I was just saying how Yu's been cold.
Comfort me!
I bet you probably said something rude.
Man, her distrust in Himari is palpable.
Yu-kun, let's go look for summer memories.
See ya!
Take care!
Maybe you should be more
mindful of what you eat.
It could affect your performance.
Is that supposed to be advice?
Everyone has their own pace.
I'm only working at the best pace for me.
That's certainly impressive.
Speaking of which, looks like
Kureha-kun got you off your game.
Let me guess. You offered
to help and she declined?
Nice theory.
But I'd say you're the one getting played.
Let's see... She tried
to blackmail you with a video?
I'd prefer to think of it as
providing her with entertainment.
You came all the way here
to keep me in check,
but I'm afraid it won't work on me.
I support Natsu and his work.
But not as much as I support Rin-chan.
Keep you in check? Of course not.
As long as Yu-kun can
pour his all into his work,
that's all that matters.
You focus on tennis, and don't
worry about anything else.
So?
Did you come up with any summer memories?
Nope.
It's such a common theme.
And way too broad.
Not to mention, I can't get
on the same page with this "client."
Try starting with scenery then!
Why not take a bunch of pictures
then try to match that with a flower later?
So the opposite of when
Enomoto-san first modeled for us?
I'm not very good at that, though.
How about Enocchi
and I come up with some ideas?
Hii-chan, you can only come up
with raunchy stuff.
No way!
I'm a high school girl, you know!
You don't usually act like it.
Do you have any ideas?
It's dusk.
I'm a guy walking home after club practice.
Together with my childhood friend.
Oh, you're storytelling?
Suddenly, rain starts falling.
We find shelter, but we're soaking wet.
I look at her sheer—
Sheer?
Her sheer shirt and pink bra!
I couldn't help myself but—
Scratch that idea.
No raunchy stuff allowed!
I don't wanna be Hii-chan's
number one, after all.
Don't be so rude.
What about you then, Enocchi?
You've always liked girly manga.
I'm sure you have a scenario in mind!
Well... I'm not picky or anything.
Anywhere's fine if it's with Yu-kun.
No one's talking
about their ideal first time!
Enocchi, you dirty girl!
Himari, no teasing!
But we're talking about her first time.
I'm good anywhere.
W-Well so am I.
I guess we'll start with obvious ideas.
Then we're both good.
Take this, Enocchi!
Hii-chan, that was cold!
They look the part.
How was that?
I got a few good shots.
Did you have to splash me that much?
My bad.
You can stop by my place
and I'll take it out for cleaning.
But your clothes won't fit me.
Are you dissing the size of my boobs?
Well played, Enocchi.
Well it's the truth.
Why I oughta!
Wanna piece of me?
I sure do!
Wait, don't Hii-chan!
Ah, to be young and wild.
It's cute, don't you think?
Yeah, I like it.
I mean, it definitely feels like summer.
But it's almost like an ad.
Not that it's bad, but I'm not
sure it goes with the theme.
How much time do we have left? Three weeks?
Yeah.
This is a lot harder than I thought.
It's like I'm thinking too hard about it.
Hey, come on! Not fair!
Take that!
Something wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, there's somewhere I wanna visit.
This is it?
It's a flower arranging
school I used to go to.
It's been a while since my last visit.
Take this! Special dive attack!
No fair, Sensei!
She's the teacher?
Grow up!
That's her.
Oh, hi there.
I see you still like gaming.
I do!
I've been hooked since
I started back when you were here.
What can I help you with today?
I was hoping you could
show me other people's work.
Wow, Natsume-kun.
That's a surprising request coming from you.
It's a long story.
Hey! Look!
Is this Hii-chan?
Yup. I used to come here for a bit, too.
Your work is meh,
but you were cute back then.
You say that like I'm not cute now.
You're not growing your hair out anymore?
It's a shame, it's so pretty.
But can't be helped if Natsume-kun
likes Inuzuka-chan's hair short.
Yu, is that true?
I-I meant it generally.
I think the general consensus is
that you look good with short hair.
But that's subjective!
So basically, you totally love me.
You're head-over-heels
in love with me, right?
I'll go short.
No, it's fine!
You have pretty hair!
I think your hair looks great!
Since you're all here, wanna
make some flower arrangements?
You wouldn't mind?
I'm sure you'll get more inspired
working with your own hands.
Wanna give it a shot, Enomoto-chan?
Yes, I'd love to.
What about you?
Oh, um... I'll just watch!
Ever since I was little,
I've sucked at making stuff.
Generally, I'm good at everything.
As long as I know all the right steps,
I'm pretty good at following
instructions. But...
I'm not good at making things creatively.
Art, cooking, flower arrangements...
Yu-kun, this is pretty hard.
Man, it's like a pork katsu bowl.
See, it's hard to make
things off the script.
If Enocchi was good on her first try,
how sad would I look?
Oh, then try this.
Think of one side while
you're getting the hang of it.
Don't worry about the back,
and use fewer flowers.
Okay. Let me try.
That's beautiful.
What do you think?
Looks great. Much better than the first try.
It's a shame, it's so pretty.
Back in middle school,
I once jumped onto Yu while he was working,
and accidentally burned my hair.
I felt so bad seeing Yu apologize.
I cut it all off when
we entered high school.
No, it's fine!
You have pretty hair!
I think your hair looks great!
Hey, Yu?
What if I had long hair, too?
What if I were feminine
and girly, like Enocchi?
Would you have eyes only for me?
That girl, Enomoto-chan.
She's the hibiscus girl, isn't she?
Sensei, you can tell?
She likes Natsume-kun too, huh?
Yup, she's committed.
She's liked him for seven years.
How about Natsume-kun?
He says he doesn't, but I know he likes her.
That's youth for ya!
Keep your cool, Inuzuka-chan.
What do you mean? I'm always cool.
Are you?
You suddenly went from
having zero romantic feelings
to becoming cling—I mean,
a girl with a crush!
N-No, I'm not!
Himari, for the battle with Kureha-san,
I think I'll do a piece on sunflowers.
It's the one from your
exhibit in middle school.
The sunflower wreath Yu made me.
It can stand its own against Kureha-san.
It'd be perfect.
I think that's a great idea!
Enomoto-san actually picked this out.
Oh, cool.
I know where you can find sunflowers!
Sunflower Festival
Sucks Enocchi couldn't come.
It can't be helped,
she has to help out at the store.
Why are you sitting behind me?
Let's sit together.
Oh, um...
Oh yeah, I have to eat breakfast.
I forgot my drink.
Here.
For real? Nice, thanks!
Are you thinking about Enocchi?
Is that why you've been
avoiding me recently?
'Cause you don't want Enocchi
to take it wrong?
That's not why at all.
Then why is it?
Why...?
It's actually because I'm
starting to see you as a girl,
and you're making my heart
beat so fast I could die.
Like I could say that!
I'm not avoiding you.
And Enomoto-san has nothing to do with it.
Bwa-ha! That's some good tea.
Seriously? What was that for?
I figured I'd test your love for Enocchi.
That doesn't make any sense.
I'll go buy you some tea
from the vending machine.
That's fine, I'll go myself.
Watch my stuff for me.
I have no clue what my best friend's
thinking and it's driving me nuts.
I can't believe how much guys change
when they fall in love.
Someone once told me that girls
and guys can't stay friends
when one of them falls in love
with someone else.
Can't be helped.
Enocchi's cuter than me.
I know I'm super pretty too, but...
Let me be very clear.
If you really wanted Natsu for yourself,
you should have taken him to Tokyo.
Natsu was prepared to leave
everything for you and you weren't.
You decided not to take him
while you had the chance.
I thought he was out of his mind back then.
But I get it now.
The nicer Yu treats me, the greedier I get.
I can't ignore that she's
much better for him than I am.
Sunflower Festival
Wow! It's a giant field of sunflowers!
Yu, keep your cool.
We gotta pick them before we check out.
Let's find the best ones
before someone takes them!
Yeah.
The sunflower has two meanings:
sweetness and vitality of life.
Araki-sensei always said balance
is the key to picking flowers.
This one's leaves are too
crooked. It feels insincere.
The flower is too big on this one.
This one's perfect.
I want Himari to wear my
piece created with this flower.
If I'm gonna make something better
than my wreath in middle school,
it's gotta be this one.
Find one?
Yeah, I like this one.
I'll still look for more, though.
Yu, guess what?
There he goes again.
Only thinking about flowers.
Once he's in the zone,
he can't hear anything else.
Sunflowers are so pretty, right Yu?
We should come with Enocchi next year.
I can't believe I'm jealous of flowers.
But still...
Yu, I love you.
Stop looking at flowers.
Have eyes only for me.
H-Himari.
Yu, did you just hear that?
Did you try to "Bwa-ha!" me just now?
Stop that, will ya?
This is serious! We have to
look for a sunflower.
It's not the right time to mess around.
Are you serious?
This can't be real.
Hey, Himari!
Is this how it's meant to be?
Even when I'm being honest,
my feelings can't reach him?
Wait up! Himari!
Then what am I working so hard for?
What meaning does my life have?
I hate it all.
I hate myself for being this way.
I hate Yu for not liking me back.
Himari! Where are you?
Right here.
There's no way he can hear me
whispering like that.
Even if the world ended
and we were the only ones left.
My voice or feelings won't ever reach him.
Himari. There you are!
What's up with you?
You've been acting weird all day.
I don't need this friendship ring anymore.
Wh-What are you...?
What am I doing, you ask?
Goodbye, Sunflower